Aryan Srivastava

+1 825-461-9281 \cdot aryansrivastava2642@gmail.com \cdot <u>Linkedin</u> Edmonton, AB, Canada

SUMMARY

University student with 4 years of experience across leadership, teamwork and problem-solving with technical proficiency in media content creation, production and management, programming language skills (C++, Python, Java, C#), strong communication and analytical skills with an extensive background in software development focusing on front end development.

EDUCATION

University of Alberta, Edmonton(AB)

Computing Science and Media Studies

Sept 2020 - Present

Jan 2019 - May 2019

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

OMS Infotech - New Delhi, India

Android Developer Intern

ctures, and emerging

- Applied and expanded knowledge of the general mobile landscape, architectures, and emerging technologies.
- Revitalized performance of applications by debugging and fixing code
- Resolved errors through close collaboration with the quality assurance team.

University of Alberta Golden Bears and Pandas - Edmonton, AB

Aug 2023 - Present

Media Production Crew Member

- Assisted with the setup and breakdown of production equipment, including cameras, 3play, Videoboard and Tricaster.
- Facilitated coordination of talent and crew members during live events, and ensured smooth transitions and seamless production.
- Assisted in editing and post-production tasks, including organizing footage and assembling video content, using 3play, Tricaster, Videoboard and Camera

University of Alberta Campus and Community Rec - Edmonton, AB Intramural Sport Activity Monitor/Referee

Sept 2022 - Present

- Compiled scores and other athletic records to maintain proper documentation.
- Participated in and attended frequent meetings and training sessions to stay up-to-date on league requirements.

Lister Hall Student Association - Edmonton, AB

Aug 2022 - Apr 2023

Floor Coordinator

- Advocated for residents/resident issues to a higher student body
- Organized, managed and planned floor events for 50+ residents.
- Liaised between floor and Student Association consisting over 2500 students.

PROJECTS

AllGasNoBrakes (APP)

Apr 2023

Geocaching interactive game where players scan QR codes around a geolocation and gain points, while being ranked against other players.

2024 U Sports Women's Basketball Championship

Mar 202

Helped record, broadcast, manage and make highlights for U Sports Women's Basketball Nationals(Final 8) with a collaborative production crew.

Canada West U Sports

Make Highlight Packages and broadcast live university sports replays for Canada West (Men and Women).

Music from Saharan Cellphones (Research)

Apr 2024

Made, edited and developed a research podcast on how the revenue, copyright and distribution for music collected from cellphones in saharan desert work in North America and other parts of the world.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Python Developer
- Android Developer Trainee
- First Aid and CPR Level C Certified
- Workplace Violence and Harassment Prevention Certified